Sync And Corrected By Pacifier....:)
@Subscene
Elegio reservations.
How may I help you?
Yes, I'd like to make a reservation for tonight,
please.
I'm sorry.
We're booked months in advance.
Okay, I understand.
Thank you very much.
Elegio reservations.
How may I help you?
Order.
That ready?
Yeah.
Thanks.
He knows the town better than anybody.
Right.
There's another place we can go.
Yeah, he'll be here.
Okay, yeah, you--
Look, you know what?
He's right there.
That's my friend.
Will you be my boyfriend--
Just for a minute?
You're not a... serial killer, are you?
That depends.
How many times does it take to get to serial?
Five?
No, we're good.
Jess.
Nicky.
Burgundy.
Very good.
It's very confusing, isn't it?
How do you know it all?
Mostly from drinking.
Yeah. The more you drink,
the more you learn.
In that case, I am, -
I am the foremost expert in jager bombs.
I will walk you through it all.
It's been a pleasure to serve you, chef oshowole.
Chef who?
Oshowole.
Yeah.
You know, it may be the roofies talking,
but this is really fun.
Thank you.
Thank you for rescuing me.
Yeah.
We showed him.
Got to respect him, though--
He left it all on the field.
That's what I'm missing out on tonight?
Yeah.
Wow. Shit.
Can I walk you somewhere?
Actually, I'm...
I'm staying here...
Upstairs.
Really?
My God.
It's my husband.
Shut the fuck up!
Jared, wait.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
Whoa, whoa!
I'll fuckin' kill you!
Jared, just let him go.
No fuckin' way.
He's fuckin' dead.
Give me one fuckin' reason why I shouldn't do it.
I'm drawing a blank.
What?
I think you should shoot me.
Let's be honest, you've been aggrieved.
Don't mess around with him, Nicky.
He's done hard time.
I've done fuckin' hard time.
- If you had any idea what I was about to do to her--
- Shut up, man.
She was gonna be no good to you after that,
so, you should really shoot me.
What the fuck?
What kind of stuff are we talking about?
Saudi bachelor-party shit.
Saudi bachelor party?
R. Kelly drop-cloth shit.
Please, come on, shoot me.
Would you stop fucking around?
I'm gonna fucking kill you.
You'd really be doing me a favor.
Cancer.
Tumor the size of a peach.
Pull the trigger.
You'll see.
Y-you got cancer?
He's onto us.
Aw, shit!
I knew this wasn't gonna fuckin' work!
You guys suck.
Just give us the money.
Or what?
Or he's gonna shoot you in the neck.
I don't want to shoot a guy with cancer.
Grandma mukulski had cancer.
He doesn't have cancer, you idiot!
You guys really boned this thing.
First of all, you got to wait till she gets my pants off.
And then you got to give me a chance to run.
That's how you get the money.
And you never drop the con.
You never break.
Die with the lie.
When did you make us?
When you stole the wallet from the bum downstairs.
Bullshit.
No, real shit.
Then why'd you come up here if you're so smart?
Professional curiosity.
And I like boobs.
You know, I figured it was a win-win.
All thumbs, sweetheart.
It was a bum lift.
It was a great lift.
Please, he was so shithoused,
you could've taken his appendix.
You suck!
You really should be more aware.
I've been behind you for two blocks.
You didn't see me?
I don't have eyes in the back of my head.
Well, if you're gonna play this game,
you might want to grow a pair.
I can take care of myself.
No, you're gonna get hurt.
Let me buy you a coffee.
I don't drink coffee.
Fine.
So, what's your thing?
Inside? Roper?
You can tell me.
Everything--
Been in this game so long.
I want to "Cannon."
That's what I want to do.
Really?
Yeah.
Yeah, okay.
My grandfather used to run a crooked game in Harlem.
Eventually, my father started shilling for him.
And, one day, they get burned.
Mobbed-up guy catches them throwing signals.
Everybody's guns come out--
Standoff.
No way out except one--
"the Toledo panic button."
What the hell is that?
You shoot your partner--
It proves you're not together.
You kill your partner?
But you hope you don't.
Does it work?
He's 0 for 3.
So your father killed your grandfather?
That's the world you're in.
Dabblers get killed.
Look, I wasn't born into this like you.
I-I was a dyslexic foster kid--
No prospects, no future.
I mean, it's a minor miracle I'm not a hooker right now.
Tutor me.
No.
Why not?
I'm headed out of town.
Well, wait, look, I can pay you--
If that helps.
Whose wallet is that?
"Dr. Peter woshilak."
We're gonna make this quick 'cause it's really cold.
Now, I'm gonna show you a few touches,
but at the end of the day, this is a game of focus.
That's very clever.
All right, now, attention is like a spotlight.
And our job is to dance in the darkness.
I didn't even feel you take that.
The human brain is slow, and it cannot multitask.
Jesus! When...
All right, I'm sure you can flip a leather on its feet,
but what we're talking about
is much more complex than that.
When did you...
Take my wallet?
You take zumba?
Well, it's actually
a really good cardio workout, thank you very much.
You're thinking with your hands.
All right, you got to get inside the Vic's head,
perceive from their perspective.
Human behavior is very predictable.
If I look at my hand,
it naturally pulls your gaze
and allows me to enter your space.
But when I look up at you,
it causes you to look directly at me.
Cute.
I touch you here, I steal from here.
I tap you here, I steal from here.
I step to here-- you're not
gonna slap my face, are you?
Why?
You would if you knew where my hand was.
Okay, I get it, I get it.
You get their focus...
You can take whatever you want.
You be safe.
So, why do I like this place?
Lots of space.
Doesn't open for a month or two.
We can tie into multiple lines, diffuse our footprint,
keep hopping dns addresses,
plus military-grade fiber.
How many bathrooms?
Fat ass Farhad is flying in.
Two-- coed.
He still got irritable bowel?
Yep.
Man, he should do a cleanse.
Horst, he is a 400-pound persian.
He is not gonna do a cleanse.
Where you been staying, Hyatt again?
Yep. I love the brunch.
You should stop by.
No, no brunch.
I'm doing a cleanse.
The horses are at the gate.
And they're off!
Hyatt rewards card in my wallet.
Admit that you're impressed.
I got your wallet,
and I found you all the way down here.
Please.
World series, final four,
the sugar bowl, super bowl--
Any big event like this is sucker central.
Well, I still found you. That's
got to count for something.
So, how many Hyatts did you have to go to?
All three, five times each.
I want in.
Maybe I'm just here to watch the game.
I asked around who ran the game in Harlem.
"The limehouse kid" is your grandfather.
Bucky spurgeon is your father.
"Father" is a very generous term.
And you're Nicky spurgeon.
They call you "mellow."
I'm all crewed up, sweetie.
Come on.
Plea-- can we--
Can we just...
Can we skip the part
where I speak through thinly veiled allure
and lead you to believe
there's some earth-shattering hump in the works?
'Cause I suck at that kind of stuff.
I just want in.
There's no earth-shattering hump in the works?
No.
I don't even get thinly veiled allure?
No baby voice?
No lingering eye contact?
I am hopeless.
That's all my favorite shit.
I'm sorry.
Can I suggest that you learn--
Professionally?
Well, I mean, you could...
You could show me...
In your room.
That is so bad.
Is it?
Does it feel sexy on your face?
A little.
It does? Okay, let's go.
Wa-- wait. Where are go--
Wait. Am I in?
No. This is Horst.
Hello, Jess.
Hi.
Nicky told me you were coming.
You're such a dick!
Yeah, he gets that a lot.
Let's go.
What are you, a size four?
Why do I have to wear this?
No one looks at your hands when
you got that working for you.
I can't breathe.
First things first--
We stick to rich folks
and no one with a cane or a wheelchair.
It's bad luck.
Tommy's the shade, gareth's the stick.
All eyes on me until I make the mark,
and once I fan them, I tug my lapel.
Two fingers means it's a prat poke.
Three fingers means the leather's an insider.
If it's a "cordeen" or an ox tongue,
I'll scratch my nose, unless I use my thumb,
which means that I am actually scratching my nose.
Anything in the left tail or the right tail,
I'll cock my head, but nowadays
"keister kicks" are 95% of it.
So you just do the touch,
and I ding the "poke" in the nearest mailbox, okay?
I'm sorry, what?
Okay, plan "B."
You two come with me.
Excuse me.
I'm so lost.
It was excellent.
You want to wire?
Let me wire.
Ponytail's your mark--
Right bridge.
Right-rear pocket.
My bad.
Come on, y'all!
That was nice.
Okay, I got this.
What?
Gimme some shade.
W-wait.
My heel keeps--
You're such a gentleman.
Thank you, sir.
Derrick knows how to treat a lady.
Married?
Dude! Come on!
Didn't mention that, did he?
No.
All right.
Thank you, boys.
You're in.
Really?!
Congratulations.
You're a criminal.
Okay, what now?
Want me to do the primer?
I got it.
Primer?
There's a flight landing every two minutes
at Louis Armstrong.
Whoever's not here for the game is here for the party.
Every one of them looking to drink big, bet big,
cheat on their spouses, and it all costs money.
There are boost teams at all the major hotels.
They hit quick and get out
before anybody ever knows what happened.
And if you think for one second I'm gonna let your mother
talk to me like that, you are fuckin' crazy!
I'm a grown-ass man!
Why are you yelling at me?
There's card games everywhere,
and they let anyone with enough cash in.
Chances are, at least one of those guys you don't know
is a mechanic who can work a deck
like Bill Clinton works a crowd.
All in.
Full boat.
I swear...
I've never had four of a kind before.
Ha! Sorry, coach.
I've never had four of a ki--
Hey, come on, coach.
Motherfucker! What the fuck?!
You win some, you lose some, right?
That's it.
Get the fuck out of here.
Come on.
Let's go. Move.
Whoo!
Yeah.
Um, it's my husband.
I'm-a kill you!
Give me my pants! Come here!
No! No just run!
Wait! Wait!
You little bitch!
Married guys are the best.
Who they gonna tell?
I'm gonna kill you!
It's my husband!
Every minute,
there's something going on down here--
Every bar, restaurant, hotel, everywhere.
Guys working alone, working in teams--
Not just cash, either.
Identity theft and credit-card
spoofing are big, too.
You can skim the data right off
a credit card in about a second.
But boosting a wallet only gives you an hour
before the Vic gets wise and the cards are canceled.
So you put the card back.
By the time the mark gets wise,
he's in youngstown arguing with his wife
over the charges we rack up before the bill comes.
A skimmer swipes the card and records the keystrokes
so you can get the pin, too.
Look. You see that?
Wow.
Did he make that?
Yeah.
A few years back,
he replaced the credit-card terminals
at about a dozen 99 cents stores in L.A.--
Took down a few million before they caught on.
What does a guy like that do with that kind of money?
He, financed his own line of gravies.
Yeah, he just--
That's his seat.
Just let him...
I'm-- I'm-- I'm sorry.
Okay. Yeah.
Who's the girl?
Her name is Jess, Farhad.
She's our intern.
You hitting that?
I'm... Right here.
No, Farhad, I'm not hitting that.
You should hit that.
Yeah, hi.
Still right here.
I'd totally hit that.
He's fucking with me, right?
Right?
She talks a lot.
Smile.
Thank you.
I'll get this loaded in.
It shouldn't take too long.
Get a digital camera.
So, we're about 30 strong.
Everybody gets a percentage.
We cover bribes and fall money
for anybody who gets pinched--
Knock wood.
We sell the atm data to a guy in Singapore.
The shopaholics here buy merchandise,
which we overnight back to ourselves
and resell on the gray market.
Yesterday, we bought 200 macbook airs.
My God.
That is incredible.
- Do you-- do you think that maybe--
- No.
We-- sell everything.
Take no chances.
So, what about the big con?
I thought you were all big time?
You mean the one where we make so much money
we all retire and get yachts and boob jobs?
Yeah, that's a fantasy.
We are in the volume business.
Safer that way.
Hey, Jen, I need a dime.
I got bit at the track.
Come on, girl.
Thank you, baby.
Clean card, clean I.D.--
Everything you need.
Thank you.
Well, don't thank me yet.
Got a lot of work to do.
Tough week ahead.
I know.
So, what now?
There's a key card in there.
I got you another place.
I think you'll like it.
Wow. Thanks.
Do you know how I can get a cab there?
I can give you a ride.
Yeah?
That'd be great.
I mean, if it's okay with you.
It's fine with me.
Is it okay with you?
Yeah.
You sure?
You seem like a pretty good driver.
You can count on me.
Can I?
Most would say no.
You seem trustworthy.
Maybe you should take that cab.
Yeah.
Okay.
Aww. Who's that?
This is my little girl, Mina.
Cute.
My son, Dani.
Aww. Sweet.
That's my wife, Lida.
Pretty.
That's my dick.
Cool.
Sorry about that.
That's okay.
That's my dog.
Aww.
Hate it.
So, you've known, um--
You've known Nicky a long time?
10 years. Why?
I was just wondering.
Okay, you got me.
We're sleeping together, okay?
Like the ancient greeks.
Actually, I don't know.
I mean, I like the guy, I do,
but people aren't really his bag,
so it's hard to tell sometimes.
Yeah, I guess you can't blame him.
I mean, he told me about that thing
with his dad and his grandfather.
That's-- that's crazy.
He told you that?
I mean, I've heard that story, but never from him.
Really?
You must throw a mean one.
Damn.
Ha ha.
I'm really gonna miss sucking his dick.
So is he.
Stop it.
All right. You ready?
Yep.
Frank! Frank!
My God!
Somebody help!
Please, please, somebody help!
Somebody get someone!
Somebody call a doctor!
I need a doctor.
Doctor, help me.
My husband's just had a heart attack.
I don't know what to do.
I'm so worried.
Frank!
Who was the cop with the wandering hands?
He was real.
He just stumbled in.
Who hits on a grieving widow?
I guess that's just how fantastic
you look in that dress.
What's a girl to do?
I can think of a couple things she could do.
Yeah, me too, actually.
I think we should start with oral.
Just saying.
Come on, man.
I'm right here.
Sorry.
Everybody.
That's so incredibly profound.
Everybody, everybody, everybody!
Can I get your attention?
What you laughing at?
A record-setting week.
And I want to say congratulations to you all.
After expenses--
$1.2 million.
Great work, great work.
After the big game's over tomorrow,
this place is gonna get bleached down.
Anything's not nailed to the floor
is going in the incinerator.
Horst here has all of your travel money.
Once you get home, I will wire you all your cuts.
Thank you, guys, really.
To Nicky!
No, no, Farhad, not forehead.
What's that mean?
It doesn't matter.
Stay juicy.
That's all of it?
1.2?
Do not let it leave your sight.
You promise?
Yeah, I promise.
No dogs or ponies, right?
Hey.
How long have you known me?
No, just look. Look at me.
Man to man.
No gambling, okay?
Yes, dear.
I'll see you when I see you.
You guys are so cute.
I'm tired.
Okay. You want to go the game tomorrow?
You have tickets?
Of course.
That's one of the perks of the business.
Do you mean...
These tickets?
Okay, you're gonna need to stop that, all right?
Stop showing off.
An exit interview?
Yes.
My God.
Are you seri--
Tell me.
So you mean like,
"Jess is a hard worker--
Honest and prompt.
I believe she'll be a valuable asset
to your team at sizzler of San Bernardino.
No, not a reference, you dick!
Criticism, constructive criticism.
R-really?
Are you serious?
Yes.
Okay.
Got a light touch.
You know, you're kind of invisible out there.
And you're calm.
You know, you get upside down, you don't panic.
You adjust.
You actually rally when the going gets tough.
Which is rare.
And I been in this for...
A really, really long time.
And I've never seen anything like you.
Thank you.
But I was actually talking about the sex.
Aw, please, there's a thousand better than you.
Whoa! Please!
I can't believe you said that!
Yeah, you're just laying there, you know?
I'm like, "come on, is this thing on?"
You're mean.
Why mellow?
What?
Why do they call you mellow?
Yeah, I don't-- no.
I don't like that name.
I know, but why do they call you that?
My dad just started calling me that.
And...
And I don't like it.
My dad, he said, um...
"There's two kinds of people in this world.
There's hammers and nails.
You decide which one you want to be."
He said, "there's no room for heart in this game.
That shit'll get you killed."
He--
He said I was soft.
So he started calling me "marshmallow."
Mellow.
Yeah.
You're a big old marshmallow, you are.
Mnh-Mnh.
I'm gonna get some more wine.
Do you want some?
Nope. I'm good.
Okay.
How did you get these tickets?
That's one of the many wonderful things about being me.
...MVP with Chicago.
Let's give a superdome welcome to Billy Canady!
Is this a bad time to mention
I don't really like football?
Yeah.
Like, the worst time possible.
I'm sorry.
It just seems like a lot of standing around all the time.
Are you kidding?
Don't you think? Like...
Well, you were really excited about the tickets.
No, I am.
I'm so excited.
I just--
I don't get the game.
I get it. All right.
You know what?
Forget football.
We can still have fun.
All right.
- Get your hot dogs right here!
- Um...
Right there.
I will bet you one dollar
that that guy does not catch that hot dog.
Down there?
Yep.
Okay.
How did you know that?
Because that guy cannot throw.
He knocked this old lady's glasses off
about 10 minutes ago.
Okay, okay.
Okay, um...
Whoo!
Down there-- shirtless guy with the body paint.
$10 says he's too drunk to get up for the wave.
Are you sure?
His team is on a drive.
Are you in or out?
I'm in.
Okay.
Don't do it.
Yes!
Really?
I know my drunks.
So, you're a fan?
You're considering yourself a fan?
Thank you.
Okay, we're even now.
All right, hold on.
No, no, a tiebreaker.
Okay.
Um... Okay.
Mamita with the short shorts.
Yeah.
See?
How many guys are gonna look at her ass
as she walks up the aisle?
Closest one wins.
End seats only?
End seats only.
At least eight.
Eight?
Three.
Five.
Can I get in on this?
Sure.
10 bucks, Mr...
Liyuan.
I say five guys look.
Sure thing.
Okay.
There's one.
Two.
Yeah.
Three.
Four, sorry.
I'm out. I'm done.
Five.
And it's six.
Come on, come on.
Six.
Seven! Yes!
I'm the closest.
I know my leches, too.
Money, money, money.
Okay, okay.
I want justice.
I want my money back.
Make another back.
Okay.
I want my change.
Pbht!
Okay, which team draws next penalty?
I don't know football.
You boys play.
Okay. Defense.
How much?
First down, rhinos.
$1,000.
Ooh.
Yeah.
I'll do the thousand.
Hut, hut!
We have holding--
Number 77 on the offense.
10-yard penalty.
Yes!
Okay, $5,000.
Do they pass or run?
$5,000?
Wow.
He's been drinking, he's been drinking.
He's definitely been drinking.
I have.
Okay, you call it.
They run.
3-18! Hut!
Yeah!
They run, they run!
Ooh. Ouch.
Yeah, ouch is right.
Ouch.
Ouch is right. Um...
On that note, I'm-a get a drink.
Yeah, me too.
Double or nothing--
Your bet.
No, I'm good. I'm good, man.
Thank you.
No, no, no, easy bet, easy bet!
They make this kick, you win.
Good odds?
They always make this kick.
You can't lose.
Come on, I want to play.
I like you.
You can't lose.
Come on, I want to play.
How much?
Double or nothing.
$10,000.
Too much?
All right. 10 grand.
3-42! Hut!
No.
Really?
I'm sorry.
Wow.
I'm such a lucky guy.
Maybe we should--
Maybe we should just get going.
I'm gonna-- all right.
Wait. Hold-- hold up.
50.
Say again?
50 grand.
Nicky.
It's all right, it's all right, okay?
Okay.
Relax.
Um, he's not gonna return the kick.
On the kickoff, he'll take a knee.
Now you make things interesting.
Okay.
We good? Nicky?
Wow.
It's okay.
All right.
Hold on, hold on, hold on.
Give me one second.
Give me a second, give me a second, give me a second.
Please.
A hundred grand.
$100,000?
Yep.
You don't have $100,000.
Yeah, I do.
You can't do that.
Next play--
Pass incomplete.
Well, I say he catches it.
Whaaa?
You've got to be fucking kidding me.
We're going.
All of it-- $1.1 million.
Nicky.
Nicky, that is my money, too.
High card takes it all.
After you.
Thank you.
Tamade!
What was that you said?
"Tomo ha de"?
What's that?
It's just an expression.
It's hard to explain.
A rough translation is...
...I am fucked!
Hey!
Sorry, friend, that's what happens
when you play with the big boys.
Hey!
Fuck.
Double it.
Man.
Dude, what are you doing?
I'm good for it.
Double it.
You got a problem, my friend.
Take those binoculars,
pick any player on or off the field,
and I will guess their number.
Any player?
That's like 100 to 1.
That's good odds for you.
$2 million.
That's fucking crazy.
I don't like it.
Okay, okay.
I'll sweeten it for you.
You pick the player...
And she'll guess the number.
What?
You're fucking crazy,
but I can't turn down free money.
You got a bet.
Alvin.
What are you doing?
Don't-- don't drag me into this.
Stop it.
What, it's not enough that you
lost everyone's money--
My money?
She sounds like my wife.
Get your hands off me.
You're sick!
Hey, hey, hey.
Come on, wait, wait.
Hey, hey, don't put your hands on her.
Steven, stop, stop!
What the hell is your problem?
Tell him to keep his damn hands to himself.
I understand, I understand.
I am sorry.
He has gotten carried away.
He likes to pretend that he is the Kevin costner
and I am the Whitney Houston.
The hell?!
Steven.
Please, he just knows that I want to play.
Let's play.
Look at me. Hey.
Please don't make me do this.
Nicky, please.
Okay.
Just pick.
Don't make me do this.
Jess.
Just let me go.
Just do it.
Pick a fuckin' player.
Please don't make me do this.
Nicky, please. Please.
It's okay.
Okay.
I got one.
Do you want me to write it down?
Nah, I trust you.
Nicky.
Then it's her turn.
Just do it.
Pick.
Pick a fuckin' player.
He's crazy, I know, but it will be his fault.
Not yours.
Let's do it, let's go!
Don't take a chance!
Fair catch if you have to!
Set up to run now!
Um, um, I don't know.
I don't...
Look, I'll give you one chance to back down, okay?
No hard feelings.
Pick.
Wow.
I guess...
I guess number...
Wait.
Number 55.
No.
No, no, no, no, no.
No fucking way!
How did you do that?!
I'm right?
Am I right?
Fuck! Yes!
You're fucking right!
I'm right?
Fucking shit!
My God.
You're fucking right.
That is crazy.
You're not mad?
No fucking way!
No?
I'm not-- Mwah!-- Mad.
We have got to go to Vegas right now.
I have a jet.
That was incredible!
Did you see what she just did?!
And you, you!
You have got some big fucking balls!
You are my new fucking hero.
Double or nothing?
Whoa! No fucking way!
Get the fuck out of my suite!
Now!
Yeah! First down, baby!
First down!
We're good! We're good!
We're good, coach.
Consider your debt settled.
I am going to kill you.
Kill me later.
I'm going to kill you!
What?!
You did great, you did great, you did great.
My God.
How did you do that?
Liyuan Tse--
Legendary gambler.
He bets on everything, anything--
Huge cash bets all the time.
Once, the bellagio put Bill Gates
out of the high-roller's suite
'cause liyuan was flying in.
He is the perfect Vic.
But how did you know who he was gonna pick?!
We told him to.
We've been telling him all day.
From the moment he left his hotel room,
we've been priming him, programming his subconscious.
He's been seeing the number 55 all day long...
On the elevator...
...in the lobby...
...even the stick pin on the doorman.
Not only that, we loaded his route
from the hotel to the stadium.
He looks out the window, primers are everywhere.
Local 55!
Now he doesn't see it, but he does.
There's no getting around it.
- He even sees Farhad.
- Let's go!
I'm trying to drive, you rhino bitch!
Fuck the rhinos!
Fuck the...
Suggestions are everywhere,
from the number of flowers in a vase
to the tramp stamp on the hooker
we sent to his room last night.
That is genius.
Yeah, and it's not only what he sees--
It's what he hears.
The mandarin word for "five" is wu.
There are 124 "Whoo-whoos"
in "sympathy for the devil."
Now, he's not registering it, but it's all there.
So when he picks up those binoculars,
looks out on the field,
sees a familiar face with the number 55 on his Jersey,
some little voice in the back
of his mind says, "that's it."
And he thinks it's intuition, and he picks.
Do you want me to write it down?
And you being in the dark was the convincer.
We call that the "little blind mouse."
I'm the blind mouse?
You're such an asshole.
You can't tell me that's 100% real.
Well, it's probabilistic.
Farhad has it at about 59%, but it's better than Vegas.
And what if he picked wrong?
Double it till it happens.
That's amazing.
You're amazing.
Nicky!
What's wrong?
You did great.
Okay.
W-what's going on?
Why are we pulling over?
Nicky?
What is this?
It's 80.
The job is over.
You did great.
You're kidding, right?
You're...
Take her to the airport.
No, I'm not going to the airport.
Wait. Can you just talk to me?
Can you just-- Nicky?
Sorry.
You did great.
What's going on?
You did good.
Answer me!
Nicky!
Wasn't expecting such a kind face.
The tech says his gizmo checks out,
but in all candor, I don't like this.
And I don't like him.
Why?
He's a con man, sir.
That's the point.
I keep my beretta well-fed.
Owens, why do you have to be so dramatic?
Invite him to lunch.
You are a man known for great skills
of persuasion and deception.
You were very hard for me to find.
Why did you take my offer?
Went broke.
My car-- 40 million euro
in R&D, easy.
Mcewen, rahal, lotus--
Any team in any class, they spend half of that.
But I have something none of them have.
A fuel-burn algorithm.
Yes. The EXR.
They all want it.
It's legal.
And my engineers promise it guarantees me a win.
That's not enough for me.
This year, McEwen is the only team standing in my way.
That is why I wanted you.
So--
This needs to be discreet.
It needs to be safe.
No holes.
I will pose as a disgruntled team engineer of yours,
offering to sell the EXR to McEwen.
What I will give him is a fake.
It just doesn't really do anything,
just gives false readings to their instruments.
It will mislead the driver enough
that you'll have a slight added edge.
A third of a second every few laps.
Imperceptible.
Just because the techs say that it checks out,
what makes you think you can convince them
that you're absolutely real,
you're-- that you're totally authentic?
You can't be dicking around here, boy.
You don't need to worry about me.
I'm extremely well-researched.
We will proceed as planned,
starting at the kickoff party tonight.
Okay.
I'll be seen drinking and boisterous
and disgruntled.
I will approach you in full view of McEwen.
An argument will ensue, I will throw my drink,
I will shove you, if that's okay wit you.
It's okay.
I'd be very surprised
if McEwen didn't approach me right there,
but if not, I will contact him.
Good.
Whatever he's willing to pay me,
I will be keeping 100% for myself,
on top of the $1 million from you.
Do we have a deal?
Yes, Mr. Garriga, we have a deal.
That's great.
Appreciate your time.
Thank you.
I'll see you tonight.
Don't say I didn't warn you.
Drama.
I'm excited.
That's right.
Estoy aqu? Por trabajo.
Do you speak English?
Yes.
Absolutely.
Yeah, but you s--
You speak good Spanish.
No, no, no, not so much.
Yes.
Why, thank you, thank you.
Okay, what can I get for you?
Look, I'm here tonight for business.
And I am a recovering alcoholic.
So when I ask you for a vodka Martini on the rocks,
if you could give me water with olives,
that would be fantastic.
Great decision, sir. Wise.
Thank you.
And the thing is, um, I-I don't even drink.
That man got me drinking again.
Okay, vodka Martini on the rocks.
On the rocks.
I wonder if "Garriga" is Spanish for "thief."
My God, what a drinker!
Who the fuck put a couch full of women
in the middle of this place?
Hey!
Where are all the black people?!
There he is, right there, the commander in thief!
But I guess you can do what you
want when you're a rich prick!
Maybe you should slow down a little?
Wait. Girl, no, no.
I just want to talk to the man.
This is a free country.
Buenos Aires is a free country, right?
No, Buenos Aires is a city.
Okay, I'm gonna go over here.
Hey!
Well, hello.
Hey.
Hello.
God, it's been a long time.
So, you--
You here with...
Rafael?
Yeah.
Yeah, he, um-- he owns one of the teams so...
Is he a mark?
No.
We're together.
Have been for a long time.
I'm out of the game.
Jess, um...
All right, about New Orleans, and just--
Nicky. No.
Nah, just the way that--
I really don't need an explanation.
I mean, if anything, I should be thanking you.
You did me a favor.
Well, that's fantastic.
He's probably wondering where I am.
Take care of yourself, okay?
You too. Be well.
Um, Nicky?
He doesn't know about my past, so...
You don't know me, okay?
Okay.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Alcohol.
Can I get a vodka, please?
Sure.
This is water.
No, sir, it's vodka.
It's water.
Sir, I know who you are.
Marcello told me about you and your condition,
so back off.
All right.
You're kidding.
Are you drunk?
Mr. Garriga is not a guy
you want to cross.
Me neither.
Now, just what part of the plan
calls for a tray full of appletinis?
You pledging a sorority?
I'm just rethinking the plan a little bit.
Goddamn prima Donna delicate science bullshit.
You are not splitting atoms here, pal.
This ain't cern.
Just do what you're being paid to do.
Shitheel.
Yeah.
Okay. Okay.
Hey!
Garriga!
God.
Don't worry.
It's just a disgruntled engineer.
I expect you have something to say to me.
My God.
Shit.
Why are you punching?
You stole from me!
Nobody steals from me!
I am such a disgruntled engineer!
Get him out of here!
Out! Get out!
Oversold it a bit, didn't you?
I was just caught up in the moment.
Aah!
Get him out.
Get rid of him.
Okay. I'm good.
Go back to the party.
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm okay.
What the hell was that?
Racing business, cari? O.
Jesus.
That's all.
Wait a minute.
You can't throw me out.
I'm staying in this hotel.
Let me see your keys.
Thank you.
Mr. McEwen would like to have lunch.
Information is on the card.
I still got it.
You ever heard of udo pappenphus?
What the fuck you looking at?
Nothing.
I'm sorry.
I meant--
Udo pappenphus was an engineer for Ferrari for many years.
Fuckin' brilliant.
One day, udo pappenphus
was found behind a berm with his throat cut.
Udo, he was that prick Garriga's man.
I want three million euro.
Well, fuck.
Jesus.
It's the EXR.
The EXR.
You're father fuckin' Christmas to me, mate.
I'm gonna need to see some proof.
You understand? Proof.
What the fuck are you lookin' at, mate?
Nothin'.
Just repeat what you said.
What, the pool go euro?
Gordon!
Get me fuckin' field glasses, mate.
They're on the--
On the thing.
Yeah.
She is a beauty.
I love these race skanks.
She's not a race skank.
'Course she's a fuckin' race skank.
Town's lousy with them.
Can we get back to business?
Please.
She's a little small on top for my taste, but...
'Kay, one man's small is another man's perfection.
It's like a "breasts are a subjective opinion" topic.
Maybe if you're bookin' a fashion show, mate.
I'm talkin' about fuckin' slapping balls, mate.
Do you-- do you want the thing or not?
I'm gonna need to see proof.
I'll contact you.
Hola.
¿Qué te gustar? A Tomar?
A Spritz, por favor.
Okay.
And a vodka and cranberry, please.
Hey, you need to put some clothes on.
Excuse me?
There's Australian people here.
What is that supposed to mean?
I'm just saying, Jess,
they shipped all those people down there for a reason.
Okay.
Gracias.
Whoa, what--?
You don't know me, remember?
And what was that last night?
Was that... About me?
Please. No.
Are you working an angle on Rafael?
No, Jess.
I'm workin' for him.
But I wouldn't trust him if I were you.
But I should trust you?
All right, Jess--
That's interesting.
Okay, Jess, come on.
Nicky, if Rafael sees us together,
I don't know what's gonna happen, okay?
He's the jealous type.
You need to stay away from me.
Fuck Rafael.
And, Nicky?
You're still an easy lift.
Stop touching my shit, Jess.
Have him punch it, mate, on the straightaway.
Well?
Looks credible.
Three million?
Yes, sir.
I can have the complete package in 48 hours.
Codes, documentation, and analysis.
No worries, mate.
No worries.
So, what's next?
Wait for my call.
Thank you.
- Hola.
Se? Or Garriga's assistant called.
She pulled a few things she said you might like.
Great.
¡Hola! Sir!
Miss?
You forgot...
...your bag.
You really should be more aware.
God. Seriously?
Malbec?
Yes, it is.
Where'd you learn that?
It's all they drink here.
And it says it on the label.
You know, Nicky, I've been thinking about all this.
And?
And, um...
Nicky...
Let me have it.
Nicky, if we just ran.
If we just....You know,
if I could slip away,
or if we could--
Yes.
Can we just...?
Whatever. Yes.
I can't.
I can't, I'm sorry.
Wait, wait, wait.
Wait, Jess.
Whatever you want.
I can keep you safe.
Nicky...
Come on, Jess.
Nicky, you taught me so much.
But I've learned a lot since then.
And I'd really...
Like to show you all the things I've learned.
Like how I learned how to play men.
Like I just played you.
How's it feel?
Wow.
Yeah.
I think you're losing it.
That was pathetic.
"I'll keep you safe"?
What was that?
That-- that was--
Does that work?
Does that get you laid?
Hey, that was not a line.
I'm not falling for your shit again.
Don't okay?
And I'm very happy.
So stay away from me.
Nice ass-o.
Nice ass. Nice ass.
Very nice, very nice.
Mi hermano.
Hey.
Let's get a steak.
A steak?
It's 9:00 in the mornin'.
Take that up with God.
How was the flight?
Jesus Christ.
They had me squeezed between two fat guys.
It sounds like you're complaining,
and you shouldn't be because I'm giving you a cut.
All right, where's this going down?
You got the piece?
It's in my bag.
Can you get it?
I'm too fat to reach it.
Watch this.
Nothin' but net.
Fuck, you all right?
Yeah.
Ya all right?
Hey there.
Farhad?!
Hi! How are you?
God, look at you!
You've lost so much weight.
I did a cleanse.
You here with Nicky?
Sort of.
Do you mind?
Please.
You must be really turned on
with all these beautiful women here.
I-I suppose.
You do more than suppose.
What does that mean?
Dear God!
I'm just sayin'.
Please never make that face again.
I don't even want to know what that means.
I think we do.
I think we don't.
God, I missed you.
Listen, everybody knows you're a lesbian.
It's completely fine.
Who knows I'm a lesbian?
It's especially fine to me.
Where are you getting this from?
Every other time you speak, I smell a vagina.
It's not true.
That's not a bad thing, believe me.
Jesus.
Okay, all right.
Listen, you got Nicky all nuts.
I do? Good.
Yeah.
I've never seen him like this.
You know, he's barely worked since New Orleans.
Seriously?
I know he's an asshole.
I mean, a really big asshole.
Yeah.
He should've handled it better.
But he's my friend, and I'm gonna bat for him.
So can you give him a break?
I don't care what Nicky told you.
I'm not falling for this shit.
Yeah, I don't think you got that right.
He seems different now, and I've known him a long time.
How do I know that?
What is that?
It's an orange.
He kept it for you all this time.
Flea market!
Shit.
That looks nice.
I can't believe you kept it.
Or found it.
Or replicated it.
I don't know with you.
No, I kept it.
Thank you.
So, Farhad said you didn't work for a long time.
Yeah, a couple years.
Just didn't feel right.
I even reached out to my dad.
I hadn't seen him in years.
I asked him if he'd ever gone straight before.
"Of course. I go straight
every time I'm on parole."
"Now drink a cup of concrete. Man up."
Solid advice.
Yes.
How's that working out?
Well, thought I was ready to work.
Then the girl walked in.
Why are you going to all this trouble, Nicky?
What do you want from me?
I can convince anyone of anything.
I once convinced a man
that an empty warehouse was the federal reserve.
So I'm good.
Yeah.
You're the best.
But what I really want
is to tell you that I've changed.
And tell you that I am sorry.
I just want you to believe me.
You know I want to believe you.
I want to believe you.
I'm different now.
I have to be getting back.
I can't do this.
I'm sorry.
Muevete.
You all right?
What happened?
I don't want to talk about it.
Did he do somethin' to you?
No.
Jess, did he put his hands on you?
Tell me what happened.
Just kiss me.
I have to leave soon.
I want you to come with me.
I know you think you love him.
But... I want you to come with me tonight.
I don't love him.
I just-- but I--
But you can't trust me.
I understand that.
If you come with me, we'll figure it out.
I want--
It's Owens.
I got to take it.
Yeah.
Where are you?
I'm in my room.
Good. I'm at the door.
He's at the do--
All right.
What?
Um...
Damn, you should've ma--
A'ight.
Give me a sec.
We're good.
Just I'll get rid of him.
Hey.
You're still sleeping?
I thought you were meeting with McEwen.
I am. Later.
There's a lazy Sunday softness to your generation.
Makes me uncomfortable.
I like to be on my feet.
I'll lie down when I get cancer.
Or if I fuck.
Both of which will be done on my back,
in case you were wondering.
Um, no, actually, I-I wasn't wondering.
But thank you for sharing that.
Sarcasm.
Another pillar of your generation.
You want to tell somebody to fuck off,
tell 'em to fuck off.
Don't say, "Gee, what a great jacket."
It's weakness.
That is a messy bed.
Yeah, I don't sleep well.
Someone here, son?
Who you callin' "son"?
You know why you don't sleep well?
No, tell me.
You with your iPhones and your smart phones
and your laptops and computers.
All of which produce nothing
but a barrage of useless information.
Fucking Twitter.
As if anyone actually cares
that you're eating a Turkey sandwich for lunch.
Sorry... Panini.
Sarcasm?
Satire.
Fuckin' panini.
Look, um...
Are we done?
You might be.
Who'd you pick up at the airport?
What, Garriga has you fuckin' following me?
I got people there.
My computer guy.
Why? Is there a problem?
There won't be because he's fucking here.
I got a little red hair on my taint
that tickles when somethin's afoot.
And lately,
I've been scratching my nethers like a fuckin' macaque.
Okay.
Look, there's no reason for anybody to panic
and start gettin' bent out of shape
because we're getting to the end.
Nice day.
Nicky!
How the fuck did you do--?
God.
Back here. 7:00.
Okay.
Guess your taint was wrong.
Enough of the pleasantries.
Hey, nice jacket.
Fuck off.
It's real.
Gordon?
Gordon!
Fuckin' you, mate.
You're my new fuckin' favorite person, fella.
I-I fuckin' swear you're fuckin'
six inches fuckin' taller
and twice as fuckin' handsome since you walked in here!
There ya go, son!
Lap it up.
My pleasure, Mr. McEwen.
I wish you the best of luck.
Friends like you, who needs luck?
Now fuck off!
Yes?
Mr. Garriga.
How did it go?
It's done.
Good.
I wish you the best of luck.
With friends like you, who needs luck?
Jess, letting you know
I've left a key for you at the desk.
See you at 7:00.
Wish you the best of luck.
With friends like you, who needs luck?
I wish you the best of luck.
Wish you the best of luck.
Friends like you, who needs luck?
Jess.
Jess?
Sorry I'm late.
What?
Nothin'.
Let's go.
Goal!
Do you really think I'm such an amateur
that I would not have someone with McEwen?
Someone to keep eyes on you?
20 years in this business
teach you never to be too careful.
He is my secret weapon.
Now imagine my surprise
when Gordon showed me what you sold to McEwen.
Not some fake softwares
as we discussed,
but my plans, my designs.
The real EXR!
Stolen from my servers, stolen from me!
What's more,
you sold it to McEwen for 3 million Euros,
but in these bags, there is 27 million Euros!
Which means you sold it to everyone!
This is my reputation!
This is my standing!
You've made me look like an amateur.
That's what you get when you hire a con man.
Thieving piece of shit.
How did you get the information?
And what did she have to do with it?
All right. Nothin'. All right?
Listen--
Tell me.
Hey.
Tell me!
Leave her the fuck alone!
I'll tell you!
I have-- I-I have a guy.
He cracked your encryption.
He found a back door into your server.
It was actually pretty easy.
You should probably fire your IT guy.
No. No! You used my login.
My password.
Computer just tries every possible combination--
Bullshit!
This generates a new password every 15 minutes.
It never leaves my sight.
How did you get it?
Who the fuck cares, man?
It's done.
Okay.
Tell me!
I want to know how!
Let her go!
How, how, how, how...
...how, how how?!
All right.
How?!
It was her!
It was her.
All right? It was her!
But she didn't know.
She didn't know anything.
Okay.
Your security was tight.
It was tighter than I expected.
I thought I could break the key, but I couldn't.
Then I saw Jess at the party.
And when I found out that the two of you were together,
I knew she was my in.
So I used her.
And I've been using her.
You see, there's a science to getting people to trust you.
With women, it's all about
emotion. Connection.
That you feel the emotion as strongly as they do.
They've been dreamin' about that shit
ever since they were little girls.
With her...
Farhad?!
...it was shared history.
How are you?
A friendly face.
Set her off balance.
Helps diffuse aggression.
You've lost so much weight!
Start discussing emotional shit.
They're disarmed.
Now they're open.
You know you got 'em
when they start to unconsciously mimic you.
A head nod.
A hand gesture.
It means you're in sync.
Sociologists refer to it as the gauchais reaction.
And then you move in for the kill.
You tell 'em how they've changed you.
I'm different, Jess.
Changed how you see the world.
Then you close.
A talisman.
Well played.
A gift that says...
Thank you.
"...you've always been in my thoughts."
The necklace had a wireless keylogger in it.
All I needed was for her to enter your room.
And when she did that, I had what I needed.
Picked up on your keystrokes.
I logged in to your computer as you...
And downloaded everything about the EXR.
I'm sorry.
But it was not her fault.
She had no idea.
She got fooled.
So why don't we let her go.
And me and you can do whatever the fuck you need to do.
I think he's lost his mind.
What's funny?
More bullshit.
What is so funny?
More lies.
What the fuck is so funny?
What's so funny?
Garriga's not my boyfriend.
What?
I hardly even know him.
She's just a race skank.
What's a race skank?
But I saw you--
No.
You-- you saw what I wanted you to see.
You taught me that, remember?
She's been driving me crazy.
Hangin' around, flirtin', teasing.
The minute I try to get her up to my room...
But I have a headache.
Cramps.
That time of the month.
It's like a crime scene.
I have scrabble in my room.
A headache. A period.
Right?
The world's longest period.
She's never even been in my room.
What?
We're so screwed.
What the fuck?
I was...
Trying to make you--
What the fuck, Jess?!
I was trying to steal his watch!
This watch?
Yes!
You're not still doing watches.
It's a piaget emperador!
It's worth 200 grand!
I'd been on him for a week.
I was waiting for my chance,
and then you showed up.
You are so much better than watches, Jess.
It's what I am good at, and I like it!
Okay, no, no, no.
When-- when you came to my hotel,
he had roughed you up.
No.
No, he had roughed me up.
She was stealing from him.
He caught me racking up charges on Garriga's credit line,
and he scared the shit out of me.
This is really fucking unbelievable.
You did all of this to make me jealous?
No. Some of it was payback
for New Orleans, but...
Yeah, to make you jealous.
I cannot believe you lied to me.
You can't believe I lied?
Can't believe it.
I can't believe it.
That's so rich from you.
So rich from you.
That's what you want to say to me right--
Yeah, 'cause there's always a job.
Are you sure?
Always a job!
'Cause I just tried to save your life!
By lying!
'Cause you're always lying, Nicky!
I don't know when you're telling the truth!
And now we're dead!
Fuck.
She's right.
You're right.
I'm...
Here's the thing about lying.
Here's the problem--
Fucks up all your options.
Paints you into a corner.
What the fuck you talkin' about?
Are you out of your mind?
And then you're forced to do some really dumb shit.
You want to die?
Well, if I die, I want to die telling the truth.
And if I lie, I want to lie like normal people lie.
I want my wife to say, "hey, honey.
Do I look fat in these jeans?"
And I want to say,
"No, sweetie.
You look terrific.
You should wear those."
That's how I want to lie.
But this...
If I'm done...
I'm gonna tell the truth.
So, Mr. Garriga,
I'm gonna tell you the truth.
And you are not gonna like it at all.
About a year ago, I pick up the phone--
- What are you--?!
- Nicky?!
What the fuck are you doing?!
I couldn't take another fucking word.
Shit!
You're next honey.
No! Are you crazy?
Look at me.
What the hell were you thinking?
Fuck you!
Now somebody's hurt.
You're fine.
You know what?
I have nothing to do with this.
Nicky, look at me.
Look at me. It's okay.
This is your mess.
It's okay. Hey.
You clean it up.
Nicky...
And keep me out of it.
Shh.
I don't know what to do.
Please, please, please.
Stay with me.
No, no, no, no.
No. Look at me.
Look at me.
It's fine. It's fine.
Nicky, look at me. Look at my eyes.
I love you, okay?
I love you. Please.
Please don't do this.
Please.
I trust you. I
you cannot leave me again.
Please do not leave me again.
Please.
No!
Aah!
What the fuck?!
You want him to fuckin' die?
What kind of a piker are you,
for chrissakes?!
Shit!
Didn't he tell you I was on the inside?
Jesus.
You must be terrified.
It's gonna be okay.
He is not gonna die.
Do you hear me?
Probably.
You see, you shoot between the third and the fourth rib,
just about eleven o'clock off the left nipple.
Here. Hold pressure on that.
Hold pressure on that.
Okay.
That misses the heart
and the major arteries.
It does, however, puncture the lung.
Let me in.
There we go.
Is this Toledo panic button?
Maybe you're not such a piker after all.
Left untreated, you got about ten minutes
before you drown in your own blood.
But... You patch it up...
You account for the cavity pressure...
Ha.
God.
And then...
There we go.
There's my boy.
Jesus.
Are you okay?
Here, honey. Here. Hold on
to that. Hold on to that.
You're okay?
You keep your eye on that.
If he can't breathe, you pull the plunger again, okay?
Okay.
Good lord, I cannot believe
that you made me shoot you.
Are you okay?
And then for what?
So that you can make
cow eyes at some race skank!
She is not a race skank!
I'm not a race skank!
You die with the lie, mellow, and you still just might.
Fuck you.
Jesus h. Christ.
Don't call me "mellow."
You're his dad?
In the loosest fuckin' possible terms.
I'm bucky, by the way.
You know, I like you, honey.
You can take a punch.
God.
And there it is.
Well, I tell you what,
you steal us a car, and I'll gather up the money.
I can't steal a car.
I've been workin' for this prick spaniard for three years,
and he's got a guy at McEwen and doesn't tell me?
What the hell ever happened to trust?
Are we almost there?
I bust my ass to get you that EXR crap and-- agh!
And then the girl walked in.
Don't be an asshole.
That any way to talk to your father?
You're not my father.
You walked away.
I took you off the street.
Taught you my trade, I taught you my passion.
Three generations of skills.
And in spite of all my earnest efforts,
in spite of all my hard work,
you turned into a good person.
Well, I just--
Go figure.
And I left you on the street for a good goddamn reason.
Because I was soft.
That just shows what you know,
you dumb son of a bitch.
We had a good thing goin'.
And then one day, like seven years in,
we're running this poker deal in Boston
and a guy pulled a gun.
Fucking gun!
Glock.
First time I'd ever seen one.
And I'm just--
I'm-- I'm paralyzed.
And all I could think about was the kid.
And I-I walked and I never looked back.
Love'll get you killed in this racket.
No place for that shit here.
No happiness with that.
You know how they say there's honor among thieves?
Well, you're no thief, mellow.
You made your choice.
So I'm taking the money.
All of it.
Mnh-Mnh.
Well, that explains a lot.
Yeah, that's dad.
No!
Yep!
See you at Christmas.
One, two, ready?
Okay, that's good, that's good.
Okay, almost there.
I don't know what we're gonna do now.
We'll be fine.
How?
Trust me.
Ooh.
I got you.