Middle East 1997
Zero, this is Zero One Alpha.
We have secured Falcon.
I say again, We have secured Falcon.
I will count from one to ten. Within
that you'll tell me what I wanna know.
Otherwise...
the number ten is the
last thing you'll hear.
One,
two,
three...
four,
five,
six,
seven,
eight...
Grenade. Get Back.
Allahu Akbar.
Shit.
Fucking missed it
How did I fucking miss it...
Merlin, I apologize for
putting you in this position.
You trained him well.
James,
your training is over.
Welcome to Kingsman,
Lancelot.
Sir
I'll deal with this mess.
Personally.
London
I very much regret that your husband's
bravery can't be publicly celebrated.
I hope you understand.
How can I understand?
You won't tell me anything!
I didn't even know he
wasn't with his squad.
I'm so sorry, I can't say more.
I would like to present you
with this medal of valor.
If you look closely on the
back, there's a number.
And as a more concrete
gesture of our gratitude,
we'd like to offer you a...
Let's call it a favor.
The nature of it is your choice.
Just tell the operator:
"Oxford's, not Brogue's".
And then I'll know it's you.
I don't want your help.
I want my husband back.
What's your name, young man?
Eggsy.
Hello, Eggsy.
Can I see that?
You take care of this, Eggsy.
All right?
And take care of your mom too.
Kingsman The Secret Service
Argentina, 17 Years Later
So sorry, Professor Arnold.
Just a tiny bit more.
Oh for god's sakes, just strip it off.
I am under very strict
instructions not to hurt you.
Look, you've made a mistake.
I am university lecturer.
I've got no money.
This isn't about money.
Our boss just wants to just talk to you.
Am I meant to find that reassuring?
He'll be here soon. He'll explain.
Do you like whiskey?
Red, get a '62 Dalmore.
Hhmm...
Honestly, this whiskey is amazing.
You will shit.
I suppose asking to borrow a cup
of sugar is a step too far?
Professor Arnold,
I'm here to take you home.
Hmm... 1962 Dalmore.
It would be a sin to spill any.
Don't you think?
Can you hold these?
Please.
Thank you.
Everything is clean.
My kind of welcome.
No stomach for violence.
I mean, literally.
I see one drop of blood, that is me..
Done.
I am like...
projectile.
Listen, I'm so sorry...
you had to witness all this unpleasantness.
Due to our uninvited guest.
But I promise you,
By the time I find out who he works for...
you and I will be the best of friends.
To the shop, please.
Arthur is in the dining room, sir.
Arthur.
Galahad.
The others were beginning to wonder if
we were going to have a double toast.
Gentlemen, I am thankful to say
that it's been 17 years...
since we last had occasion
to use this decanter.
Lancelot was an outstanding
agent and a true Kingsman.
He will be sorely missed.
To Lancelot.
To Lancelot
I intend to start the selection process
for Lancelot's replacement tomorrow.
I want each of you to propose a candidate
and have them report to UK HQ
No later than 9 p.m. GMT.
Thank you.
Merlin.
Come in.
Lancelot was investigating
a group of mercenaries
who were experimenting
with biological weaponry.
Glasses, gentlemen. Please.
Uganda, 2012. Synthetic Cathinone.
You put it in the water supply
of a guerrilla army base.
Rage, cannibalism. Multiple fatalities.
Chechnya, 2013.
Insurgents turned on one another.
Indisputable, the work of our mercenaries
but no trace of any chemicals of any kind.
So what happened to Lancelot?
He tracked them to this
property in Argentina.
And while he had them under surveillance,
he became aware that they
had effected a kidnapping.
So he executed a solo rescue mission...
which failed.
This is his last transmission:
KIDNAP VICTIM IS PROFESSOR JAMES ARNOLD
- Who is he?
- Some climate change doomsayer.
Expounded something called Gaia theory about
the world healing itself or some such.
But what's curious, is
he's not actually missing.
This is Professor Arnold.
At Imperial College, this morning.
It's all yours. And don't forget
your membership proposal.
Try picking a more suitable
candidate this time.
17 years
and still evolving with the times remains
an entirely foreign concept to you.
Need i remind you, I wouldn't be here
if it weren't for that young man.
He was as much Kingsman material
as any of them.
More so.
But he wasn't exactly one of us, was he?
Let's face it, Galahad.
Your little experiment failed.
With respect, Arthur, you're a snob.
With respect?
The world is changing.
There's a reason why aristocrats
developed weak chins.
Eggsy?
Eggsy, come here.
- Got any whistler, babe?
- No.
Why don't you do your mamma a favor,
Go down to the shop and get some.
- Get 'em yourself.
- Oi, What i have said to you about speaking to Dean like that?
Three's a crowd, isn't it
Why don't Dean's poodle go?
I tell you what,
Why don't you take this and get the stuff
and get yourself some sweets?
And while you're gone, we'll show your
mother how three can be good a company.
Thanks babe.
Come here.
Here we go.
Is it better?
If Dean treat your mum's so
bad, why doesn't she leave him?
Low self-esteem.
That's her problem.
Fuck off, why would she
have low self-esteem?
Eggsy mum's a world fit.
- No offense pal.
- It's all right.
- One of these days I'm gonna smash his face in.
- Are you mental, cuz?
He'll just get that lot to do you
and then pretend he knew nothing
about it.
Oy, you think you can chat
shit about us and we wont do nothing,
just because our governor
bangin' Eggsy's mum?
Pretty much, yeah.
Leave it, let's just go, man.
It's not worth it.
You boys have outstayed your welcome.
Leave.
What?
I'm sorry about that bruh.
Yeah... muck.
They weren't fucking worth it, Boys.
It's freezing.
Why are we walking?
- You jacked his fucking car keys, bruh?
- Yeah, now we're gonna nick his car.
Fucking shit.
Hold on boys.
Hey, That's my fucking car.
Oi, Oi, Eggsy.
I swear,
you're in fucking trouble.
Floor it, Eggsy.
Hey yeah Dean, look it's me.
Eggsy just stole my fucking car.
I've come out of the pub, He's done 15 about
donuts on my fucking face and then he's drove off.
No, I cant, He's disrespecting me
and so he's disrespecting you.
Thickie.
Foxes are vermin, cuz.
You should've driven it over.
I should've done a lot of things.
I'll sort this, get out of the car.
Get out of the fucking car.
Eggsy, there is no such thing
as honor among thieves.
Now you can start giving me some
names of the boys you were with...
Or you go down.
It's up to you.
I want to exercise my
right to a phone call.
Well, I hope it's to your mom...
to tell her that you're gonna to be
18 months late for your dinner.
Customer complaints.
How may I help you?
My name's Eggsy Unwin. Sorry, Gary Unwin.
And I'm up shit creek, I'm in
an urban police station and
my mom said to call this number
if ever I needed help...
I'm sorry, sir. Wrong number.
Wait, wait
Oxford's not Brogue's?
Your complaint has been duly noted,
and we hope that we've not lost you
as a loyal customer.
Yeah...
Shit, What?
Yes, I totally understand.
Eggsy
Would you like a lift home?
Who are you?
The man who got you released.
That ain't an answer.
A little gratitude would be nice.
My name is Harry Hart.
And I gave you that medal.
Your father saved my life.
So before you was a tailor, were
you in the army?
Like an officer?
Not quite.
So where was you posted, Iraq or something?
Sorry, Eggsy. Classified.
But my dad saved your life, yeah?
The day your father died,
I missed something.
And if it weren't for
his courage, my mistake
would have cost the lives
of every man present.
So I owe him.
Your father was a brave man.
A good man.
And having read your files, I'd think he'd be
bitterly disappointed in the choices you've made.
You can't talk to me like that.
Huge IQ, great performance
in primary school.
And it all went tits up.
Drugs, petty crime, never had a job.
Do you think there's a lot
of jobs going around here?
Doesn't explain why you
gave up your hobbies.
First prize, regional
under tens' gymnastics
Two years in a row. Your coach had you
pegged as Olympic team material.
Yeah and when you grow up
around someone like my
step-dad, you pick up new
hobbies pretty quick.
Ah of course, always someone else's fault.
And who's to blame you for
quitting the Marines?
You were halfway through training,
doing brilliantly, but you gave up.
Because my mum went mental.
Banging on about losing
me as well as my dad.
Then we wouldn't be cannon
fodder for snobs like
you, judging people like
me from your ivory towers.
With no thought about why we do what we do.
We ain't got much choice, you get me?
And if we was born with the same
silver spoon up our arses...
we would do just as well as you,
if not better.
What the fuck you doing here?
You taking a piss?
Some more examples of young men who
simply need a silver suppository?
Ya, they are exceptions. Come on.
Nonsense, we haven't finished our drinks.
After you nicked his
car, Dean says you're a
fair guy I don't give a
shit what your mum says.
Listen, boys.
I've had a rather emotional day,
so whatever your beef with Eggsy is,
and I'm sure it's well founded...
I would appreciate it enormously
if you could just leave us in peace...
until I finish this
lovely pint of Guinness.
You should get out of the way, Granddaddy.
Or you'll get hurt a lot.
He ain't joking, you should go.
Excuse me.
If you're looking for another rent boy,
they're on the corner of Smith's Street.
Manners...
maketh...
man.
Do you know what that means?
Then let me teach you a lesson.
Are we going to stand around here all day,
or are we going to fight?
You fucking... You fucking...
"STUN"
Amnesia
Sorry about that.
Needed to let off a little steam.
Heard, yesterday a friend of mine died.
He knew your father too, actually.
I do apologise, Eggsy. I should not
have done this in front of you.
No. Please.. I won't say nothing,
I swear.
If there is one thing I can
do, it's keep my mouth shut.
- You won't tell a soul?
- I swear, I've never crossed anyone out.
Is that a promise?
- On my life.
Much appreciated, Eggsy.
You're right about the snobs.
But there too, there are exceptions.
Best of luck with everything.
In celebrity news, The Richmond Valentine
movie premiered in Hollywood, last night.
The story of the Internet
billionaire's rise to power
is expected to be this
award season's hot ticket.
One notable absence
from the red carpet was
Iggy Azalea, still missing
three days after...
Eggsy, just go. Please
because he's gonna...
- Please don't hurt him.
- Fuck off!
Shut the fuck up.
Who was with you in that fucking pub?
- I want to know the name of the geezer you was with.
- I was not with anyone.
I don't know what you're on about.
- Fucking tell me his name.
- I don't know what you're fucking on about.
You listen to me, I want to know who you
was with in that pub. You Understand?
I want to know his fucking name.
I don't know what you're fucking on about.
Fuck off.
I could kill you right now and no one
in the the world will know it.
But I would.
I have enough evidence
on your activities to
have you locked up for
the rest of your life.
Mister Dean Anthony Baker.
So I suggest you leave the boy alone.
Or I shall be forced to deliver it
to the appropriate authorities.
Eggsy, meet me at the tailor's
I told you about.
What the fuck's going on here?
Eggsy, you fucking maggot...
Here's we gotta arrest him.
Hey... hey... hey
Come here.
You wanker!
I'll have you soon.
I've never met a tailor before.
But I know you ain't one.
Come with me.
Come on here.
What do you see?
Someone who wants to know
what the fuck is going on.
I see a young man with potential.
A young man who is loyal.
Who can do as he is asked,
and who wants to do something
good with his life.
Did you see the film "Trading Places"?
No
How about "Nikita"?
"Pretty Woman"?
All right.
My point is, the lack of a
silver spoon has set you
on a certain path, but
you needn't stay on it.
If you're prepare to adapt and learn,
you can transform.
Oh, like in "My Fair Lady"?
I know you're full of surprises.
Yes, like "My Fair Lady"
Only in this case, I am offering you the
opportunity to become a Kingsman.
A tailor?
A Kingsman agent.
- Like a spy?
- Of sorts.
Interested?
You think I've got anything to lose?
Since 1849, Kingsman Tailors have clothed
the world's most powerful individuals.
In 1919, a great number of them had lost
their heirs to World War 1.
That meant a lot of money
going un-inherited.
And a lot of powerful men with a desire
to preserve peace and protect life.
Our founders realized
that they could channel
that wealth and influence
for a greater good.
And so began our adventure.
An independent international
intelligence agency
operating at the highest
level of discretion.
Without the politics and bureaucracy...
that undermine the integrity of
government run spy organizations.
A suit is the modern gentleman's armor.
And the Kingsman agents
are the new knights.
- How deep does this fucking thing go?
- Deep enough.
Shit. We're late.
Your father had the same look on his face.
As did I.
Come on.
- Galahad.
- My code name.
Late again, sir.
Good Luck.
In you go.
Fall in.
Ladies and gentlemen, my name is Merlin.
You are about to embark
on what is probably the
most dangerous job
interview in the world.
One of you and only one of you
will become the next Lancelot.
Can anybody tell me what this is?
- A body bag, sir.
- Correct.
- Charlie, isn't it?
- Yes, sir.
In a moment, you will
each collect a body bag.
You will write your
name on that bag.
You will write the details of your
next of kin. On that bag.
This represents your
acknowledgment of
the risks that you
are about to face...
as well as your
agreement to strict
confidentiality, which
incidentally if you break...
will result in you and your next
of kin being in that bag.
Is that understood?
Excellent.
Fall out.
Roxanne. But..
Call me Roxy.
- I am Eggsy.
- Eggy?
No, Eggsy
Eggy... and where did
they dig you up?
You know we are not allowed
to discuss who proposed us.
No need to bite his head off.
Charlie's only making
conversation, right Charlie?
I'm Digby.
Digby.
Eggy, this is
Rufus.
Rufus, Eggy.
So Eggy, are you
Oxford or Cambridge?
Neither.
St. Andrews? Durham?
Oh wait, I think we may have met.
Did you serve me at the McDonalds
in Winchester Service Station?
No.
But if I had, I give you an
extra helping of secret sauce.
It's definitely St. Andrews.
- Just ignore them.
- Do you need a pen?
Cheers.
- Amelia, isn't it?
- Amelia,
- Eggsy
Hi Eggsy!
Don't take any notice
of those guys.
That's what I told him.
It's just scare tactics.
Classic army technique.
No one's gonna die.
Shame.
Great, so you don't know,
the CIA don't know.
Nobody knows who this guy is?
Fine.
Seriously, it's fine.
Well, it's not really fine but
it's not why I'm here.
Hell man, you know me?
Money's not my issue.
I could have retired straight
out of MIT, fucked off
to some island and let
the business run itself.
Nobody told me to try
and save the planet.
I wanted to.
Climate change research, lobbying,
years of studying, billions of dollars.
And you know why i quit?
Because the last time I checked,
the planet was still fucked.
Hence, my epiphany.
Money won't solve this.
Those idiots who call
themselves politicians,
they bury their heads
in the sand...
and stood for nothing but re-election.
So I spent the last two years trying
to find a real solution.
And I found it.
Now, If you really want to make
the world a better place...
I suggest you open
your fucking ears
because I'm about
to tell it to you.
Go on, Mr. Valentine.
I'm still listening.
As long as you agree to all my terms.
No one panic. Listen to me. Stay calm.
- Use snorkels.
- Use snorkels?
- Shower heads.
- Shower heads?
She's right. Go. Fucking go.
And what about pulling the fucking door?
Congratulations
on completing your first task.
Charlie, Roxy, well done.
For those who 're still confused
If you get a breathing
tube run the U-bend of
a toilet, you have an
unlimited air supply.
Simple physics. Worth remembering.
Eggsy,
Well done for spotting
that was a two-way mirror.
He is probably seen enough of 'em.
Yeah you can all wipe those
smirks off your faces.
Because as far as
I am concerned,
every single one
of you has failed.
You all forgot the most important thing:
Teamwork.
So much for classic army technique.
35,
5.
That's it.
Hello?
Can I help you?
Yes, I have a question
about anthropogenic force.
Really? Well, it's actually
quite fascinating.
My colleague died
trying to rescue you.
And I'm sure you saw how
well-trained he was.
So I suggest you tell me who kidnapped you
and why they let you go.
I have no idea what you're talking about...
I can not say, it was...
Oh for god's sake, I barely touched you.
How man are...
"IMPLANT ACTIVATED"
Fuck that guy, whoever he is, I'm gonna...
He made me kill
Professor Arnold.
Goddamn loved Professor Arnold.
Well the good news is
we know the emergency and
surveillance systems work.
You know what is not good news?
"My colleague died."
That's what he said.
This is an organization
and they are all over us.
Whoever you spoke to...
I told you, I am in contact with the
KGB, MI6, Mossad and Beijing.
They all insist he
wasn't one of theirs.
Beijing.
So freaky how there's no recognizable name
for the Chinese Secret Service.
Now that's what you call a secret, right?
You know what?
Fuck it. We need to speed things up.
Bring the product release forward.
They are only halfway into production.
Speeding it will cost a fortune.
Do I look like I give a fuck?
Just get it done..
As some of you will have
learned last night:
Teamwork is paramount here at Kingsman.
We are here to enhance your skills,
test you to limits.
Which is why you're gonna pick a puppy.
Wherever you go, your dog goes.
You will care for it,
you will teach it.
And by the time they are fully trained,
so will you be.
Those of you who are still here, that is.
Do you understand?
Choose your puppy.
A poodle?
What?
They are gun dogs.
Oldest working breed.
Easy to train.
A pug?
It's a bulldog, isn't it?
It would get bigger though, wouldn't it?
Ssshhhit
His MRI shows no signs of concussion.
No direct brain trauma at all.
How much longer can he be out?
That's the million-dollar question.
We don't know what he was
exposed to in there.
What about Harry's footage?
It didn't stream to
his home terminal?
Encrypted and uncrackable.
If and when he comes round,
you might wanna have
a word with him about
sharing his password.
Is he gonna be alright?
We need to have patience, Eggsy.
But there is hope. Okay?
If I were you, I'd concentrate
on your training.
Make it through the
test, make him proud.
Come on, J. B. Come on.
I am not coming last cause of you.
J. B, I'll shoot you, goddamn.
I'll fucking shoot you.
Merlin said we're not allowed to hold you.
Bollocks.
Water.
Come on then.
Eggsy, you forget it.
Oh what's wrong mate,
can't take a joke?
Seriously, you'll get turned out and it's
just not worth it.
Maybe I don't give a fuck
about getting kicked out.
Really? Come on, you player.
Charlie, fuck off.
Yeah, go on, walk away.
Dickhead.
Come on, J. B.
It's all right.
You have exactly one hour
to complete the test.
Starting now.
- New target. 800 meters.
- It's unbelievable. You're still here.
Lingering on like some big steaming shit
that just won't flush.
Roger that.
Target identified. And how
about you shut the fuck up.
Positive discrimination.
It's worth it.
Like those fucking steak
cooks who go down seaways
because their mum's a
one-legged lesbian.
You don't know fuck-all about my grades.
Oh forgive me. I'm sure
you're highly educated.
Fire when ready.
How's that for positive discrimination?
I wanna thank you both for listening.
And I really, really appreciate
your traveling all this way,
Your Royal Highness.
And you too, Prime Minister.
I think this is quite brilliant.
It is absolutely brilliant.
You are completely crazy.
I'm sorry, Your Royal Highness...
but you got a big role to play...
in getting the Scandinavian
region back on track.
You're popular,
inspirational and
you have the power to
galvanize the people.
Now whether you're on board or not...
I am going to have to insist
on getting you somewhere I
can ensure your safety.
How about you, Prime Minister?
You in or out?
Well, I think it's
about time that
a politician did
something that...
actually made a difference.
Too true.
Take her away.
Drink?
Why not?
Wait, help me.
Do not worry. No harm will
come to the princess.
Well I'm Republican anyway,
so it really doesn't matter.
Release the princess.
Okay, you're done.
Not too bad, right?
I hardly felt a thing.
Welcome aboard.
The pleasure is all mine.
Ever heard of knocking?
Only when I'm casing
a place to rob.
Amelia said you wanted to see me.
Hope J. B.'s training is going
as well as yours is.
Sit.
Congratulations on making it
to the final six candidates.
Your test results are even
better than I could've hoped.
Come in.
Eggsy, I need to have a
private conversation.
You're dismissed.
Nonsense, let him observe.
He'd learn a thing or two.
As you wish. Take a look at this.
Fucking hell. That's his... harry.
You blew up his head?
Its a bit much, isn't it?
Actually, the explosion was caused
by an implant in his neck.
Here. Under that scar.
Did my hardware pick up the
signal that triggered it?
Fortunately, yes.
Unfortunately, the IP address
it traced it to is registered
to the Valentine Corporation.
It's not much of a lead.
They have millions of employees worldwide.
No, Richmond Valentine is a genius.
Did you not see his announcement today?
No.
We each spend on average
$2,000 a year on cellphone
and internet usage.
It gives me great
pleasure to announce,
those days are over.
As of tomorrow, every man, woman and child
can claim a free SIM card...
compatible with any cellphone,
any computer and...
utilize my communications network
for free.
Free calls. Free internet. For everyone.
Forever.
Valentine's assistant has
the same implant scar.
I think Mr. Valentine and I
shall have a tête-à-tête.
He's having a gala dinner next week.
I'll get you an invitation.
You need to be careful though.
Since you were out, hundreds of VIPs
have gone missing.
No ransom notes,
exactly like Professor Arnold.
Then I suggest you make my alias
somebody worth kidnapping.
You don’t like heights?
Yes it's okay I've done it before.
Probably alright if I don't think of it.
Hey, you'll be alright,
You're top of the class.
Listen up, your mission is to land in the
target without the radar detecting you.
If I read you on the radar or
you miss the target, you go home.
Is that understood?
Drop zone coming up. 20 seconds.
Here we go.
- I really don't think I can do this.
- Of course you can't.
Get to the back and I'll
show you how, yeah.
Eggsy, Eggsy.. wait. Hang on.
Roxy, just stop fucking about.
Follow me, yeah?
Roxy, it's now or never.
Jump.
Good girl, Rox.
I'm glad you made it.
My my, you're all very cheerful.
You really think it was gonna
be that straightforward?
Any idiot can read a heads-up display.
A Kingsman agent
needs to be able
to solve problems
under pressure.
Like what to do when one of your group
has no parachute.
No parachute? Who?
Fuck. Which one?
What do we do?
I told you. Aim for the target
coming under the radar.
And I hope not to be
scraping one of you up.
But if I do have to and
you're inside the target...
means I'll be very impressed.
Everybody listen, I've got a plan.
Pair up. Grab the closest person to you.
Rufus, come on.
Oh fuck.
Rufus!
Oh shit! I can't
Fuck!!!
Fucking cock.
Rufus, you wanker.
We are an odd number now.
- Quick, make a circle.
- Fuck. Right boys. Let's do it.
We'll pull our cords one by one.
When we know who's it, the person
on the right grabs him.
Ok, Eggsy
Good plan, Eggsy. You have 30 seconds.
Come on now. Hurry up.
You first.
Fuck
OK, Me next.
See you on the ground, boys.
Now me.
Roxy, no matter what happens now,
I've got you. Alright?
OK, Eggsy
You first, okay?
Yep
Shit.
Oh Shit.
Rox
Hugo, Digby,
You don't land in the K
then you're not in the K.
Rufus, you opened too soon.
You were all over the radar.
All three of you, pack your bags. Go home.
Eggsy, Roxy, congratulations.
You have set a new record.
Opening at 300 feet,
that's pretty ballsy.
Well done on completing another task.
Follow.
Sorry sir, but why the fuck
you choose me as the gimp?
- Am I the expendable candidate?
- No no no. You don't talk to me like that.
If you have a complaint, you came here
and you whisper in my ear.
You need to take that
jape off your shoulder.
Mr. DeVere. It's a pleasure to meet you.
I am sorry. I seem to
have my dates muddles up.
Oh no no. I canceled the
gala because of you.
Anybody willing to
donate that much
deserves their own dinner.
Come in.
Thank you.
Gotta admit, I was really
intrigued to meet you.
There are not many
billionaires I do not know.
I don't doubt it.
Obviously, I have had my people
looking into your affairs
and that's some pretty
old money you're from.
How'd your folks make it?
Property, mostly.
Property in the markets.
Nothing personal, if that's your concern.
No, I'm just in to find out what kind of
person you are. I'm sure you understand that.
I most certainly do.
Hope you're hungry.
I'm famished.
Good. Grab a seat.
I'll have the Big Mac, please.
Great choice.
But nothing beats two cheeseburgers
with secret sauce.
Tastes great with
this '45 Lafite.
A classic pairing.
May I suggest Twinkies with
1937 Château d'Yquem for pudding?
I like it
So you want to donate to my foundation?
You are aware that I wind
things down in that area, right?
Climate changes affect us all,
Mr. Valentine.
And you are one of the few powerful people
who seems to share my concerns.
I stepped things down because
I wasn't getting anywhere.
Every bit of research kept
pointing to the same thing.
The carbon emissions are a red
herring, and we are past the
point of no return no matter
what remedial actions we take.
You know your shit.
I sometimes envy the blissful
ignorance of those less well-versed
in their shit.
As Professor Arnold always said:
"Humankind is the only virus
cursed to live with the
horrifying knowledge of its
host's fragile mortality."
There are not a lot of
people who know about him.
Do you like spy movies, Mr. DeVere?
Nowadays, they're all a little
serious for my taste.
But the old ones... marvelous.
Give me a farfetched
theatrical plot any day.
The old Bond movies. Oh, man.
Ah, When I was a kid,
that was my dream job.
A gentleman spy.
I always felt the old Bond films were
only as good as the villain.
As a child, I rather fancied
a futuristic colorful megalomaniac.
What a shame we both had to grow up.
Bon appétit.
Just give me a couple of days
to think over your proposal.
I'll have my people get in touch with yours
and it's all good.
Thank you for such a "Happy Meal".
- Well, you want me to follow him?
- Nah.
I put a nano tracker gel in the wine.
We'll know his every move for the next 24
hours. Finally find out who he works for.
Valentine didn't let
me out of his sight.
All I got was this,
on the way in.
South Glade Mission Church
is a hate group based in Kentucky.
The FBI have been
monitoring them for years.
Do you think Valentine
is a supporter?
No evidence yet of a direct connection,
but I'll keep looking.
Oh, by the way,
the ever-growing list
of missing persons...
Now includes Scandinavian Royalty.
Royal Crown Princess Tilde.
Just let me out, you PSYCHO!
I told you, you're free
to go anytime you want.
As long as you agree
to my conditions.
I don't agree.
And I am never ever going to agree!
Enough yet.
Bitch.
The list of missing celebrities and dignitaries
has continued to grow in recent weeks.
And world leaders are coming under
increasing pressure to provide answers.
We are doing everything in our
power to find princess Tilde.
You know, governments and security forces
worldwide are working together...
to find the person behind these abductions.
In other news, people all
over the world continue to
wait in line day and night
to get their free SIM card.
Mrs. P. You get one?
Yeah, I've been queuing up all day.
This unprecedented giveaway
by the philanthropist Richmond Valentine...
has already seen over a
billion cards distributed.
At ease.
So you thought you were
done for the day, huh?
Probably not.
- A party?
- Tonight. In London.
- Who is this?
- Your target.
Your mission is to use your
NLP Training to win over
the individual in the
photograph in your envelope.
And when I say "win over", I
do mean in the Biblical sense.
Easy
Most girls love a bit rough.
We'll see about that, yeah.
Who is that anyway?
I just had to come over
and say "Amazing eyes".
- You wearing color contacts?
- No.
- You so are
- Oh my god. 'Negging'. That's hilarious.
I haven't had anyone try
that since the 90s.
Excuse me?
"Negging". Saying something
negative to a pretty
girl in order to undermine
her social value.
Its supposed to make you
want to win his approval.
Absurdly basic neurolinguistic
programming technique.
Is it just me or does this
champagne taste a little bit funny?
That's an acquired taste, mate.
- I think it's just cheap.
- Get one of these instead. They're delicious.
You know, if you're interested in ornamental
techniques, this guy is textbook.
See what he just did? Its
called an 'opinion opener.
He got you talking with
a neutral question...
got all of us involved in the conversation,
so that you crave individual attention.
Nah, I'm just saying that the
champagne tastes weird...
Lady Sophie, Montague Herring,
phone call for you at reception.
- Be right back.
- See you in a bit, yeah.
- Good job, Rox. I'm feeling a bit rough.
- You alright?
Sorry to eavesdrop...
but there is a much easier way to
guarantee getting someone home.
Rohypnol.
Or even something stronger.
Who the fuck are you?
Where am I?
This knife can save your life.
Fuck
My employer's got two
questions for you, Eggsy.
What the fuck is Kingsman?
And who is Harry Hart?
I do not know what the fuck that is.
Oh Eggsy, I just killed
two of your friends
because they gave me the
same bullshit answer.
Just cut the fucking ropes, please.
Eggsy, is the Kingsman worth dying for?
Fuck You
Congratulations.
Bloody well done.
- How'd the others do?
- Roxy passed with flying colors.
Charlie's up next.
Want to watch?
Yeah, alright.
Is Kingsman really worth dying for?
No fuck, it isn't shit
I'll tell all you want, please.
Chester King's Arthur,
head of a spy agency;
It's called Kingsman.
Thank you Charlie. Much appreciated.
Come on, It wasn't the fucking deal
I had such high hopes for you.
You are a bloody disgrace.
I'm so sorry
Please untie me.
Untie yourself.
Arthur, please.
Anyone?...No
Galahad, Percival. Congratulations.
You candidates have reached the
final stage of the testing process.
As tradition allows, you now have
24 hours to spend with them.
Eggsy, you should know
your father reached this point.
From now on,
there are no safety nets.
Understood?
Good. Dismissed.
Charlie, time to go home.
Fuck you
My fucking dad's gonna hear about this.
"To pee or not to pee?"
That was the headline the day after I
diffused a dirty bomb in Paris.
- "Germany 1 - England 5."
- I missed that game.
I was breaking up an undercover
spy ring at Pentagon.
My first mission.
I foiled the assassination
of Margaret Thatcher.
Not everybody had thanked you for that one.
The point is, Eggsy, nobody thanked
me for any of them.
Front page news, and all these occasions
were celebrity nonsense.
Because it is the nature of Kingsman that
our achievements remain secret.
A gentleman's name should appear in the
newspaper only three times:
When he's born, when he
marries and when he dies.
And we are, first and foremost, gentlemen.
Pretty fucked then.
Its like Charlie said,
I am just a pleb.
Being a gentleman has nothing to do with
the circumstances of one's birth.
Being a gentleman is something one learns.
Yeah, but how?
Alright, first lesson,
you should have asked me
before you took a seat.
Second lesson,
how to make a proper martini.
Yes, Harry.
Goddamn it. It fucking hurts.
You are the one who asked for
a biometric security system.
What's wrong with
a simple switch?
A simple switch?
This is an extremely
dangerous machine.
It should only be operated by someone
responsible and sane as me.
Bad shit can happen
if it falls into the wrong hands.
SYNC MAIN TERMINAL
- Are we done here? Shit
- No, now this one,
for the test of the church.
This one just has a short range.
A simple switch will do.
So you gonna teach me how to talk proper
like in 'My Fair Lady'?
That'd be absurd.
Being a gentleman has nothing
to do with one's accent.
Its about being at ease in one's own skin.
As Hemingway said:"There is nothing noble
in being superior to your fellow man."
"True nobility is being superior
to your former self."
Now, the first thing every gentleman
needs is a good suit.
By which I mean a bespoke suit.
Never off the peg.
And Kingsman suits are
always bulletproof,
So let's get you measured.
And whether you get the job
or not, you will have a
lasting and useful memento
of your time at Kingsman.
I'm so sorry, sir, but a gentleman
is completing his fitting.
Fitting Room 2 is available.
One does not use
Fitting Room 2...
when one is popping one's cherry.
Perhaps I'll show you Fitting
Room 3, while we wait.
- So we going up or down?
- Neither.
- Is this it?
- Of course not. Pull the hook on your left.
Oh, Yes
Very very nice.
You're going to need a pair of shoes
to go with your suit.
An Oxford is any formal shoe,
with open lacing.
This additional decorative
piece is called broguing.
- "Oxford's, not brogue's."
- Words to live by, Eggsy.
Words to live by.
Try a pair.
Your weapon scores are
excellent, by the way.
These you're familiar with.
And this is our standard issue pistol.
Its quite unique. As you all
see it, it also fires a
shotgun cartridge for use in
messy close-range situations.
How do they feel? Now do your
very best in impersonation
of a German aristocrat's
formal greeting.
No, Eggsy.
That is sick.
In the old days, they had a
phone in the heel as well.
How do I get it back in?
It is coated with one
of the fastest-acting
neurotoxins known to
man, so very carefully.
I had a lot of fun with this.
One of our finest examples
of chemical engineering.
Poison. Harmless when ingested.
But at a time,
convenient to you...
it can be remotely activated.
Primed.
Lethal.
And what about these? What do these do?
Electrocute you?
- Don't be ridiculous. It's a hand grenade.
- Shut up...
If you want to electrocute someone,
you'll need a signet ring.
A gentleman traditionally wears
the signet on his left hand, but
a Kingsman wears it on whatever
hand happens to be dominant.
If you touch the contact behind the ring,
it delivers 50,000 volts.
And what about them? What
makes them so special?
Nothing. That technology is caught up
with the spy world.
Put it back, Eggsy.
Perfect timing. Gentleman's just finished.
Mr. DeVere.
What a coincidence.
You're totally the
reason I'm here.
When you left my house, I was searching for
that dope-ass smoking jacket you had on.
And since I'm going as Royal Ascot, apparently
you need one of these penguin suits...
Here I am. What are you doing here?
What's up man? Richmond Valentine.
This is my new valet.
I was just introducing him to my tailor.
Another coincidence. So am I.
- Did you have any chance to think further on my proposal?
- Most definitely.
My people will be getting in
touch with you very soon.
I guarantee it.
A word of advice: Ascot requires top hat.
I might suggest Lock & Co.
Hatters,
St. James.
"Lox", as in smoked fish?
As in "locked up".
I have trouble understanding
you people sometimes.
You all talk so funny.
Gentlemen, would you look after him please?
Now this is a dope-ass top hat.
Gazelle, lets go Ascotting.
Your hat is fine Bill, come on.
Don't make me late for the queen.
Come on, Gazelle. We're gonna be late.
How far is Ascot? How far?
Merlin said you wanted
to see me, sir?
Sit down.
Pretty dog. What's his name?
J.B.
- As in "James Bond"?
- No.
- "Jason Bourne"?
- No. Jack Bauer.
Bravo.
It pains me to admit it,
Eggsy, but I think that
one day you might be as
good a spy as any of them.
Take it.
Shoot the dog.
This weapon is live.
Give me the gun.
At least the girl's got balls,
Get out.
I knew you couldn't make it.
Go home.
Merlin, send in Roxy, please.
Welcome to Kingsman, Lancelot.
Oh god, I've been so worried about you.
Oh my Dais, look how big you've got.
- Where is he?
- I am fine.
Eggsy, please please, just
don't get involved...
No, I should never have
left you on your own.
This stops right now.
Be right back.
Oh Mugsy, so you're back?
You nicked a fucking taxi now?
Yeah. Can I have a word about my mom's
black eye?
You wanna have a word with
me, you get out of that cab,
I'll knock you straight back
down on your fucking arse.
Tell your muppets to go inside,
then I'll get out.
Go on lads. There'll be two hits:
Me and him and then he and the floor.
Come on in, you prick.
Let's see what you got, eh.
What are you doing?
Remote car.
Now you've gone all bollocks.
Come on, he'll beat my fucking mother.
Come back when you've grown a pair. Mugsy.
You throw away
your biggest opportunity
over a fucking dog.
And then you humiliate me
by stealing my boss's car.
You shot a dog just
to get a fucking job?
Yes, I did.
Mr Pickle here reminds me of that
every time I take a shit.
You shot your dog
and had it stuffed?
You fucking freak.
No. I shot my dog and
then I brought him home
and continued to care
for him for the next eleven years
until he died of pancreatitis.
- What?
- It was a blank, Eggsy.
It was a fucking blank.
Remember Amelia?
Yeah
She didn't drown. She works in our tech
department in Berlin. She's fine.
Limits must be tested. A Kingsman only condones
the risking of a life to save another.
As my father saved your life
even though your fuck-up cost his?
What you've get him stuffed here also?
Can't you see that everything I have done
has been about trying to repay him?
Harry, listen to this.
Valentine's alarm is
saying something of note.
You know what I love about pen and paper?
Nobody can hack into this shit.
Our worldwide tour was a complete success.
We have total coverall.
- Like when all your numbers in bingo are crossed out.
- Bingo!
Bingo, the game.
You have played Bingo, right?
Do I look like I play bingo?
Point is...
if our tests go well at church tomorrow,
we are good to go.
South Glade Mission Church.
- Merlin, get the plane ready.
- Will do
- I am so sorry. I'm gonna do..
- You should be.
You stay right there.
I'll sort this mess out when I get back.
"Kentucky, U.S.A"
And I say to you: Bear witness.
Watch the news. Watch the news.
AIDS, floods
The blood of the innocents spilled.
And yet there are those
who doubt this is the wrath of God.
Our filthy government condones sodomy.
Divorce, abortion.
And yet some still doubt,
this is the work
of the Antichrist.
You do not have to be a
Jew, a nigger, a whore...
or an atheistic science
loving evolution spouter.
Charming sermon.
Can you see Valentine anywhere?
So my friends, although he is a just God,
he is justly...
The One and there will be no turning back
Are you sure we
are out of range?
We're over a 1000 feet away.
What's wrong?
- What if the calculations are wrong?
- You just have to trust me.
Jews, nigger, fag lovers.
And the devil is burning
them for all eternity.
Excuse me.
Where are you going?
Hey, what's your problem?
I am a Catholic whore,
currently enjoying congress
out of wedlock with my
black Jewish boyfriend...
who works in a military abortion clinic.
So hail Satan. And have a
lovely afternoon, madam.
Oh shit, he's leaving. I'm
starting the test now.
Hope enough of these
freaks have our SIM cards.
Ask you to sit down...
Leave this church like the infidel you are.
You will eat your babies.
You will drown in the blood of the Lord.
He will cast.
Holy fuck.
Shit, I can't watch this. Get over here.
Jesus...
Galahad, can you hear me?
Harry, Harry.. what the heck is going on?
Just turn the volume down please.
I didn't expect it to
be that effective.
What kind of response
are we talking of?
100%.
So everyone's been infected
Whether they have SIM card or not?
And its added benefit of
wiping out the Kingsman.
Not yet.
Oh you need to see this.
What did you do to me?
I had no control.
I killed all those people.
- I wanted to.
- Clever, isn't it?
In simple terms, its a
neurological wave that triggers
the centers of aggression
and switches off inhibitor.
Transmitted through your nasty
free SIM cards, I assume?
You know what this is like?
Its like those old movies we both love.
Now I'm gonna tell you my whole plan...
and then I'm gonna come up with some
absurd, convoluted way to kill you...
and then you'll find an equally
convoluted way to escape.
That sounds good to me.
Well, this ain't that kind of movie.
No
Is he dead?
That's usually what happens when
you shoot someone in the head.
- It feels good, Right?
- No no, it does not feel good. It felt fucking awful.
What? You just killed how
many people in that church.
This is one guy.
No..No... No, they killed each other.
Okay, send off the
countdown clock
This party starts tomorrow.
Arthur?
- Are you there?
- Sadly, I am.
Assemble the Kingsman.
Can't you see that everything I have done
has been about trying to repay him?
I see a young man
with potential,
who wants to do something
good with his life.
Kingsman
Arthur, Harry is dead.
Galahad is dead.
Hence, we have just drunk a toast to him.
Well then you know what
that psycho's doing.
How many people in the world
have got those SIM cards?
Valentine can send a signal
to any of them.
All of them. If they all go homicidal at
the same time, then..
Indeed, and thanks to
Galahad recordings
we have Valentine's confession.
The intelligence has been passed on to the
relevant authorities.
Our work is complete.
And a most distinguished legacy
for our fallen friend it is too.
And that's it?
Come sit down, boy.
This is an 1815 Napoleonic brandy.
And we only drink it
when we lose a Kingsman.
Galahad was very fond of you.
And on this occasion, I think it is
acceptable for us...
to bend the rules a little.
- These are all Kingsmen?
- Yes, our founder members.
I want you to join me in a toast.
To Galahad.
Harry said you don't like
to break the rules, often.
Why now?
You're very good, Eggsy.
Perhaps I'll make you my
proposal for Galahad's position.
Provided we can see eye to eye
on certain political matters.
Can you guess..
What this is?
I don't have to.
Harry showed it.
You click it, I die.
I thought that brandy tasted a bit shit.
Bravo.
Valentine won you over. Somehow
Once he explained, I understood.
When you get a virus, you get a fever.
That's the human body raising its
core temperature to kill the virus.
Planet Earth works the same way:
Global warming is the fever...
Mankind is the virus.
We are making our planet sick.
A cull is our only hope.
If we do not reduce our
population ourselves,
there's only two
ways this can go:
The host kills the virus,
or the virus kills the host.
- Either way...
- The result is the same:
The virus dies.
So Valentine's gonna take care
of the population problem himself.
If we don't do something, Nature will.
Sometimes a culling is the only way to
ensure that this species survives.
And History will see Valentine as the man
who saved humanity from extinction.
And he gets to pick and choose
who gets culled, does he?
All his rich mates, they get to live. And then when
he thinks its worth saving, he's keeping them safe.
- Whether they agree with him or not.
- And you, Eggsy.
In Harry's honor, I am inviting you to
be part of a new world.
It's time to make your decision.
I would rather be with Harry.
Thanks.
So be it.
The problem with us
common types is,
that we are light fingered.
Kingsman's taught me a lot.
But slight of hand...
Yes, they're our our founder members.
I had that done already.
You dirty little fucking prick.
It's okay, Lancelot. Put it down.
It's verified.
Arthur's phone's just
received an update text about
getting to safety. We
don't have a lot time.
- What you gonna do?
- The question is what we gonna do.
God knows who's in Valentine's
pocket and who's not.
We've no choice.
We are gonna have to deal
with this ourselves.
Follow me.
- The fuck is this?
- I have no idea.
What you're playing with...
is a prototype personal
trans-atmospheric vehicle.
It was developed as part of
Reagan's Star Wars project.
Its pretty basic, but
it should still work.
We're going to take out one
of Valentine's satellites.
We're gonna break the chain.
Stop the signal.
It will take him a couple
of hours to reboot it.
Which buys us enough time for you to get me
into Valentine's mainframe...
so I can shut it down.
Lancelot, you are going to be using it.
Get into your halo suit.
Swedish Air Force
The Swedish Prime Minister requesting
permission to land.
Permission granted.
- Please.
- Thank you.
- So how many more are we expecting?
- Not many. Most have their own bunkers.
I figure we're just getting
really nervous once.
Welcome, Prime Minister.
It seems the implant can emit
some kind of counter signal...
to ensure the wearer remains unaffected
by the waves from the SIM card.
The waves that turns everyone
into a psycho killer?
Quite. But what they probably didn't
tell anyone...
Is that it can also super heat
their soft tissue at his command.
Valentine's selected his chosen few
to get the countdown warning.
He had to be sure that it didn't
blow up to the wrong people beforehand.
And how does this help us right now?
It doesn't. Roxy, here we go.
The higher you go,
The more the balloons expand.
When you reach the edge of the atmosphere,
they will explode.
You need to deploy your missile
just before that, okay?
The edge of the atmosphere.
And once you've deployed, you'll need
to release for descent fast.
Good luck.
You can do this, okay?
Eggsy, come on.
Time is not our friend.
Getting in with Arthur's invitation,
you gonna need to blend in.
- I'm supposed to be Arthur?
- His invitation's in his phone.
Give them this and give
his real name: Chester King.
- And what about you?
- I'm the pilot. I'm gonna stay here.
Is that gonna fit me?
A bespoke suit always fits.
Just be grateful Harry
had it made for you.
Get dressed.
The fuck's wrong with them?
I don't know. Could have something
to do with mass genocide?
Give me the mic.
Everybody listen up.
What the fuck wrong with you people?
I just want to remind you that today
is a day of celebration.
We must put aside
all thoughts of death,
and focus on birth.
The birth of a new age.
We mustn't mourn those who
give their lives today.
We should honor their sacrifice.
She got my number to call me back...?
And their role in saving
the human race.
We must put aside doubts and guilts.
You are the chosen people.
When folks tell their kids the story
of Noah's Ark, is Noah the bad guy?
Is God the bad guy?
How about the animals marching two by two?
Of course not.
Yes, that's it. So let's turn
that frown upside down.
Eat, drink and party.
And I'll see you all in the new age.
Rox, its me. How's the view?
- Hideous.
- Mine's pretty sweet.
- They made you one of these suits yet?
- No, not yet.
That's something to
look forward to then.
We're coming up on Valentine's base.
Gotta go.
Good luck.
Looking good, Eggsy.
Feeling good, Merlin.
This is November 2-4-7 Charlie Kilo
requesting permission to land.
Permission is granted.
Fuck me.
Eggsy, We're on.
Chester King.
Mr. King, welcome.
I'm sure you've adhered to Mr Valentine's
strict no weapons policy...
but if you don't object..
- Of course.
- Thank you
Do you have any luggage?
Congratulations, Mycroft. You just
graduated from my pilot to my valet.
- Cheeky.
- Understood?
Good.
Thank you.
Eggsy, find a laptop.
Get me online.
The clock is ticking.
And remember: Try to blend in.
Would sir care for a drink?
Martini. Gin,
not vodka, obviously.
Stirred for 10 seconds while glancing
it an unopened bottle of vermouth.
Thank you.
Merlin, you clock in this?
Yes I am. Stay focused.
Lancelot, you're doing great.
Not much further to go.
Yes, Merlin.
Eggsy, get me online. Now.
Yep. I'm on it.
Lancelot, you're approaching
your altitude limit.
These balloons won't
last much longer.
Start to engage missile.
The society is dead.
Long live society.
Amen to that.
- Morten Lindström.
- Chester King.
How'd you get online?
Oh well, it's a closed network, you see.
For authorized connections only.
I've got a fix on the satellite.
Do you have the correct time?
I think I'm still
on my last time zone.
Oh yeah. Lets see now.
Eggsy, I'm in. Get
your arse back to the plane now.
I'm on my way.
Lancelot, good luck.
Firing in three, two...
Nice and slow.
What the fuck are
you doing here?
Well, my family was naturally invited.
Obviously.
Now get the fuck up. Slowly.
Lancelot, hurry up and fire.
The other balloon is gonna blow.
Yes, Merlin. I've nearly got it.
Give me a second.
Valentine, I've caught a fucking spy.
V-Glass, zoom.
It's that young valet.
Son of a bitch.
Got it.
Oh shit. Sound the alarm.
I'm not taking any chances.
Okay, you send out two minutes warnings.
I'm starting the override.
Countdown initiated.
- You see him?
- Right here.
Eggsy, take a left. Two guards up ahead.
Lancelot, release now.
Eggsy, straight ahead and then right.
There's two more.
All right, everybody on your feet.
Countdown to V-Day.
Welcome into new age.
Eggsy, next left. Got a narrow tunnel.
Here we go.
Ten...
Nine...
Eight...
Seven...
Six...
Five...
Four...
Three...
Two...
One...
Biometrics Authorized
System Failure
Nice. Well done, both of you.
It's not working.
It's supposed to be working. What the fuck?
Yes, Well done, Rox. Good girl.
We've lost one of our satellites.
System Analysis Complete
Oh no no. There's no way
I can hack past that.
Biometric Security Detected
What's going on?
Is there a problem?
Come on, there's no need for guns.
I'm just a pilot.
Fuck.. Merlin.
Get in here.
Come on.
- Let's go the fuck out of here.
- We can't.
I can't get into
Valentine's machine.
It's got biometric security.
You're gonna have to get in there and
make sure his hand never touches that desk.
You taking a fucking piss?
I'm afraid not.
Let's me have that then.
This is mine.
I'll show you yours.
Good choice.
How long to relink
the satellite chain?
It can take an hour.
Maybe two.
Bullshit. Just bring these
two closer together.
But that's not yours.
V-glass, call E-man.
E, its V. Listen man, I got a
little hiccup on this end.
I need a piggyback.
One of my satellites just went
down but is right next to one of yours.
You read my mind. How long before you
make that happen?
Go.
We should be coming back online.
10%
Valentine using someone else's satellite.
He's gonna reconnect the chain.
Its gonna take him no time at all.
Its at 20%.
Eggsy, Valentine's got a present for you.
Get a move on.
- Is that Kingsman kid dead yet?
- Not yet. But he will be soon.
Good.
Merlin, I'm fucked.
As am I.
They're coming at me from both sides.
I'm out of options.
Rox, I need a favor.
Call my mum and tell her to
lock herself away from Dean
and the baby.
And tell her I love her.
Merlin, you remember those implants you
said were of no use to us?
Any chance you could turn them on?
My turn to play, Valentine.
Oh no. What the fuck is he...
I cant stop this.
ACTIVATE SECURITY IMPLANTS?
Yes, please.
SECURITY IMPLANTS ACTIVATED
Nooo....
That was fucking spectacular.
Merlin, you're a fucking genius.
What the fuck is happening out there?
Aren't you that princess
who went missing?
Can you get me out?
Well if I do, will
you give me a kiss?
I've always wanted
to kiss a princess.
If you get me out right now,
I will give you more than just a kiss.
You motherfucker.
Did you really I
was stupid enough
to implant one of those
things in my own head?
What are you? Fucking crazy?
All those innocent people
killed and for what?
You didn't stop shit.
Fine, I have locked the door.
What do you want me to do now?
As I said, put your daughter in the
bathroom and throw away the key.
It's still happening.
- You fucking insane?
- Just do it.
Eggsy, the signal's started.
Get Valentine's hand off
that bloody desk now.
Sorry, love. Gotta save the world.
If you save the world,
would you do me in the asshole?
I will be right back.
Good luck.
London.
Rio.
Get down.
You did it.
This glass is not gonna hold long.
You stay here.
- Merlin, quickly how do I get up there?
- Keep shooting. I'm find a route.
Understood.
We are back up.
This is great.
Eggsy, fucking get on with it.
Kick his ass, darling.
Seoul, Caracas, Mumbai.
Kill that motherfucking...
Eggsy, the world is going to shit.
- Is he dead yet?
- Not yet.
Stop playing with your foot. Kill him.
Gazelle.
Gazelle!
Come on.
Kill him.
Well done son.
Yes!
Yes! Eggsy
Well done, Eggsy.
And you, Lancelot.
I am sorry. Mommy
would never hurt you.
Mommy would never hurt you.
I am so sorry.
You okay?
Harry would be proud of you, Eggsy.
He was right.
'Sup man?
Is this the part where you say some
really bad pun?
Its like you said to Harry:
This ain't that kind of movie, bro.
Perfect.
Eggsy, where you going?
There's no need for champagne
We have got lots on the plane.
Did you save the world?
Yes I did.
So, You gonna come in?
Yes, I am.
Merlin, this cell's locked.
How do I get in?
26-25.
Merlin, you're the governor.
You owe me, Eggsy.
Eggsy
Oh my word.
Michelle, turn that shit off, its
turning me nutty.
I rather like that song.
Leave it on eh, Mom.
Mugsy's back.
You finally come to have that
word with me, have you son?
Or are you going to run
away again and pretend
you're getting another
coat dress like that?
You mean this?
No.
I know this bloke who's just taken
over a tailor shop up on Seville Road.
He's got me a job, Mom.
Comes with a lot of perks.
Including a house.
Come and live with me there, Mum.
- Come on.
- Sit down, you.
Only place she'll be visiting is
you in fucking hospital, do you hear?
Just leave him alone.
Eggsy, go please. Just go away.
All right
Yes, just do as mommy says.
Why don't you ask that tailor
friend of yours to knock up
a nice chicken costume,
it would suit you ya mug.
As a good friend once said:
Manners...
maketh...
man.
- Dean?
- Shut the fuck up.
Eggsy, I'm gonna shove your manners
up your fucking...
So...
Are we going to stand around here all day,
or are we going to fight?